Guide to the American Veterans Committee records, 1942-2002 MS2144
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subjects, 1946-2000; MS2144 Series 1
  - Other veterans' groups, 1946-2000; MS2144 Series 1, Subseries 8
    - National Association of Concerned Veterans, 1972-1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - National Association of Veterans Programs Administrators, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - National Council of Veterans Associations in Canada, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - National League of Cities/Reveille, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - National Urban Coalition, 1973-1977 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - National Urban League, 1967-1980 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - New York veterans' organizations - Ruth Young, 1992-1999 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Operation MEDIHC, 1972-1973 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Verband der Heimkehrer (Association of Returnees, POWs, and Family Members of Missing Germans), 1954 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Leadership Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Veterans' organizations, 1975-1987 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Veterans' organizations, 1992-1993 (Box 253, Folder 14)
    - Veterans for Peace, 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Service Organizations, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Vietnam veterans contacts, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Wisconsin veterans, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - YMCA, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- AVC Bulletins, 1945-1999; MS2144 Series 2
  This series includes a nearly full run of AVC's main publication, summarizing the group's activities and positions both nationally and locally. The Bulletin was first published biweekly, then monthly, then bimonthly.
  AVC Bulletins from 1946-1968 are bound by year; others are foldered by year.
  - Bulletins, 1945 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins, 1946 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1946 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins, 1947 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1947 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1948 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1949 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1950 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1951 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1952 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Bulletins, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1953 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1954 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1955 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1956 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1957 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1958 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Bulletins, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1959 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1960 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1961 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1962 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1963 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1964 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1965 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins (bound), 1968 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Bulletins, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Bulletins, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Bulletins, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Bulletins, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Bulletins, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Bulletins, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Bulletins, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Bulletins, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Bulletins, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Bulletins, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Bulletins, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Bulletins, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Bulletins, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Bulletins, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Bulletins, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Bulletins, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Bulletins, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Bulletins, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Bulletins, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Bulletins, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Bulletins, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Bulletins, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Bulletins, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Bulletins, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Bulletins, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Bulletins, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Bulletins, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Bulletins, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - AVC Bulletin cartoons, 1949, undated; Series 2 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    These are loose cartoon drawings and it is unclear which issues of any these were used within.
- Official statements, 1946-2001; MS2144 Series 3
  This series includes official statements by AVC on issues of concern to veterans. Such statements offer a concise introduction to the variety of issues in which AVC was involved over time. Correspondence written to lobby members of Congress is also included in this series.
  Contains six formats: Testimonies before Congress, Statements to Congress, Press releases, Reports, and Platforms/resolutions (written and voted upon at AVC conventions), and Congressional correspondence.
  Some AVC testimonies are contained within the bound proceedings of the congressional hearings in which they were a part.
  - Testimonies, 1940-1949 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Testimonies, 1950-1954 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Testimonies, 1955-1959 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Testimonies, 1960-1963 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Testimonies, 1964-1966 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Testimonies, 1967-1969 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Testimonies, 1970-1974 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Testimonies, 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Testimonies, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Testimonies, 1980-1983 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Testimonies, 1984-1989 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Testimonies, 1990-1993 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Testimonies, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1947-1949 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1950-1954 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1960-1969 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1970-1990 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 2002 (Box 253, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Platforms/ Resolutions, 1946-1962 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Platforms/ Resolutions, 1963-1979 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Platforms/ Resolutions, 1980-1986 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Platforms/ Resolutions, 1987-2001 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Platforms/ Resolutions, 2002 (Box 253, Folder 16)
  - Platforms/ Resolutions [1/2], undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Platforms/ Resolutions [2/2], undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1948-1958 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1958-1968 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1980-1986 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1986-1992 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Reports, undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Official Statements, 1946-1999 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Official Statements, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - AVC statements in Congressional Record, 1946-2000 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - AVC statements in Congressional Record, 1946-2000; Series 3 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - AVC statements in Congressional Record, 2001 (Box 253, Folder 17)
  - Congressional correspondence, 1948-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Congressional correspondence, 1968-1979 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Congressional correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Congressional correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Congressional correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 253, Folder 18)
  - Congressional correspondence, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Bound testimonies, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 03/1963-05/1963 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Bound testimonies, 05/1963-07/1963 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Bound testimonies, 05/1965-07/1965 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 03/1965-09/1965 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Bound testimonies, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Bound testimonies, 1967-1968 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 12/1969-07/1970 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Bound testimonies, 08/1970 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Bound testimonies, 11/1970-12/1970 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 02/1971-03/1971 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Bound testimonies, 06/1977 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Bound testimonies, 06/1977 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 06/1977-10/1977 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Bound testimonies, 09/1977-03/1978 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Bound testimonies, 03/1978-05/1978 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 11/1979-06/1980 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Bound testimonies, 07/1981 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 08/1982 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Bound testimonies, 03/1983-07/1983 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Bound testimonies, 05/1983-05/1984 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Bound testimonies, 10/1985 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1946-1997; MS2144 Series 4
  This series includes minutes and agendas from a variety of AVC national meetings. The following bodies and events are represented: National Administrative Committee, National Board, National Conventions, National Executive Committee, National Affairs Commission, National Planning Committee, and the Trustees of the Deavenport Trust.
  More material from AVC events, such as printed programs from the National Conventions, is available in Series 8.
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1959-1987 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 02/27/1949 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 06/06/1949 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 03/14/1952 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes Appendix A Memorandum, 03/14/1952 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 04/14/1952 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 05/10/1952 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 08/01/1952 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 09/19/1952 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 10/10/1952 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 10/10/1952 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 11/21/1952 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 02/27/1953 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 03/27/1953 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 06/05/1953 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 08/07/1953 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 10/30/1953 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 01/08/1954 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 02/27/1954 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 05/15/1954 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 06/25/1954 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 08/07/1954 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 09/10/1954 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 10/29/1954 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 11/17/1954 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 01/14/1955 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 02/04/1955 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 02/17/1955 (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 03/05/1955 (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 05/13/1955-05/14/1955 (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 07/27/1955 (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 01/27/1956 (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 04/20/1956 (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 06/22/1956 (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 10/05/1956 (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 12/07/1956 (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - Nat'l Admin. Committee Minutes, 01/25/1957 (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/25/1958 (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/27/1958 (Box 93, Folder 39)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/20/1958-09/21/1958 (Box 93, Folder 40)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 02/21/1959-02/22/1959 (Box 93, Folder 41)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/15/1959 (Box 93, Folder 42)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/17/1959 (Box 93, Folder 43)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/19/1959-09/20/1959 (Box 93, Folder 44)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 01/30/1960-01/31/1960 (Box 93, Folder 45)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/02/1960-04/03/1960 (Box 93, Folder 46)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/10/1960 (Box 93, Folder 47)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/12/1960 (Box 93, Folder 48)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/17/1960-09/18/1960 (Box 93, Folder 49)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/03/1960-12/04/1960 (Box 93, Folder 50)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 03/03/1961-03/05/1961 (Box 93, Folder 51)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/21/1961 (Box 93, Folder 52)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/30/1961-10/01/1961 (Box 93, Folder 53)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/01/1961-12/03/1961 (Box 93, Folder 54)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 03/02/1962-03/04/1962 (Box 93, Folder 55)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/01/1962-06/03/1962 (Box 93, Folder 56)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/26/1962 (Box 93, Folder 57)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 10/13/1962-10/14/1962 (Box 93, Folder 58)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/08/1962-12/09/1962 (Box 93, Folder 59)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 03/08/1963-03/10/1963 (Box 93, Folder 60)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/30/1963 (Box 93, Folder 61)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/02/1963 (Box 93, Folder 62)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 08/02/1963 (Box 93, Folder 63)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/07/1963-09/08/1963 (Box 93, Folder 64)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/07/1963-12/08/1963 (Box 93, Folder 65)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 03/07/1964-03/08/1964 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/15/1964 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/17/1964 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/26/1964-09/27/1964 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/05/1964-12/06/1964 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 03/06/1965-03/07/1965 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 10/15/1966 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/15/1967-04/16/1967 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/30/1968 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/23/1968-11/24/1968 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/13/1968 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 02/15/1969-02/16/1969 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/03/1969-05/04/1969 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/15/1969 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/06/1969-12/07/1969 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 10/24/1970-10/25/1970 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 02/20/1971-02/21/1971 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/11/1971 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/13/1971 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/11/1971-09/12/1971 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/18/1972 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 10/07/1972-10/08/1972 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 01/27/1973 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/08/1973 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/10/1973 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/04/1974 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/28/1974 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/30/1974 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/16/1974 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/25/1975 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/27/1975 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/29/1975 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/22/1975 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 01/31/1976 (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/15/1976 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/26/1976 (Box 94, Folder 36)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/27/1976 (Box 94, Folder 37)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/13/1976 (Box 94, Folder 38)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 02/26/1977 (Box 94, Folder 39)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/30/1977 (Box 94, Folder 40)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/17/1977 (Box 94, Folder 41)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/19/1977 (Box 94, Folder 42)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/10/1977 (Box 94, Folder 43)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/08/1978 (Box 94, Folder 44)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/02/1978 (Box 94, Folder 45)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/04/1978 (Box 94, Folder 46)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/11/1978 (Box 94, Folder 47)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 12/15/1978 (Box 94, Folder 48)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 02/10/1979 (Box 94, Folder 49)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/07/1979 (Box 94, Folder 50)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/03/1979 (Box 94, Folder 51)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/17/1979 (Box 94, Folder 52)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/19/1980 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/30/1980 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/01/1980 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 10/11/1980 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/09/1981 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/05/1981 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/07/1981 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/07/1981 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/19/1982 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/04/1982 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/06/1982 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/16/1983 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/24/1983-06/26/1983 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 01/16/1984 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/14/1984 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/29/1984 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 07/01/1984 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/16/1984 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/16/1984 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/13/1985 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/29/1985 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 08/12/1985 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/18/1986 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/19/1986 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/30/1987 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/08/1987 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 10/05/1988 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 03/25/1989 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/20/1989 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 09/24/1989 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 11/18/1989 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 04/06/1990 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/11/1990 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/14/1991 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 05/15/1992 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 06/03/1993 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 08/19/1994 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 10/25/1995 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Board Meeting minutes and agenda, 1995 October; Series 4 (Box 261, Folder 13)
  - Board minutes, 1995; Series 4 (Box 261, Folder 14)
  - National board, 1996; Series 4 (Box 261, Folder 15)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 08/26/1997 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Board materials, 1997; Series 4 (Box 261, Folder 16)
  - National Board Minutes, 1994-1995, 1997; Series 4 (Box 261, Folder 12)
  - Nat'l Board Minutes, 2003-2005 (Box 253, Folder 19)
  - First Constitutional Convention Minutes pages 1-80, 06/14/1946-06/16/1946 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - First Constitutional Convention Minutes pages 81-180, 06/14/1946-06/16/1946 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - First Constitutional Convention Minutes pages 181-294, 06/14/1946-06/16/1946 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Second Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 1-150, 06/1947 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Second Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 151-300, 06/1947 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Second Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 301-450, 06/1947 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Second Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 451-543, 06/1947 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Second Nat'l Convention Workshop Session, 06/19/1947-06/22/1947 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Third Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 1-150, 11/25/1948-11/28/1948 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Third Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 150-300, 11/25/1948-11/28/1948 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Third Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 301-450, 11/25/1948-11/28/1948 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Third Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 451-600, 11/25/1948-11/28/1948 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Third Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 601-697, 11/25/1948-11/28/1948 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Fourth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 1-150, 11/24/1949-11/27/1949 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Fourth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 151-266, 11/24/1949-11/27/1949 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Fourth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 267-375, 11/24/1949-11/27/1949 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Fourth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 376 - 597, 11/24/1949-11/27/1949 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Fourth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 751 - 789, 11/24/1949-11/27/1949 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Fifth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 1 - 150, 05/31/1951-06/03/1951 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Fifth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 151 - 300, 05/31/1951-06/03/1951 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Fifth Nat'l Convention Minutes pages 301 - 456, 05/31/1951-06/03/1951 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 05/17/1957 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 06/28/1957 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 09/06/1957 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 11/27/1957 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 01/10/1958 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 03/15/1958 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 06/06/1958 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/04/1958 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 11/07/1958 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 12/12/1958 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 02/09/1959 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 04/06/1959 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 06/12/1959 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/08/1959 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 09/18/1959 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/04/1960 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 10/04/1960 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 04/06/1961 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 06/23/1961 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/10/1961 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 09/06/1961 (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 11/03/1961 (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes Summary, 11/03/1961 (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 01/05/1962 (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 02/02/1962 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 03/30/1962 (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 04/20/1962 (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 06/03/1962-06/15/1962 (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 07/12/1962 (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/09/1962 (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 09/14/1962 (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 11/02/1962 (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 01/18/1963 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 06/28/1963 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/02/1963 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 10/04/1963 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 11/01/1963 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 01/03/1964 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 02/07/1964 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 04/10/1964 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 06/26/1964 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 08/14/1964 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 10/04/1964 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 11/06/1964 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 01/14/1965 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Exec. Comm. Minutes, 02/19/1965 (Box 100, Folder 14)